Guide to the Alice Kavounas Papers, 1962-2010
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
Alice Kavounas Papers
1962-2010
Kavounas, Alice
0.5 cubic feet (2 boxes)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
Correspondence, printed material, photographs, and audiotape relating to Kavounas' time as a student at Vassar College as well as her work as a poet.
Biographical Note
Member of the Vassar Class of 1966 and poet. Her poems have been published in several literary journals and anthologies and she is the author of The Invited and Ornament of Asia.
Scope and Content Note
Correspondence, printed material, photographs, and audiotape relating to Kavounas' time as a student at Vassar College as well as her work as a poet.
Access
This collection is open for research according to the
regulations of the Vassar College Archives and Special Collections Library
without any additional restrictions.
Related Materials
Many of Kavounas' publications are available in the
Vassar College Alumnae/i Collection.
Subject Headings
Organizations:
Vassar College--Students
Subjects:
Poets, American
VCL Categories
Literature and Writing; Vassar College
Encoding Information
Encoded by Laura Streett, May 2012.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Alice Kavounas, January 2012.
Container List
- Letters home — from Vassar, 1963 - 1964 (Folder 1.1)
- Letters home — from Vassar, 1964 - 1965 (Folder 1.2)
- Letters home — from Vassar, 1965 - 1966 (Folder 1.3)
- Letters home — from Europe, 1965 Summer (Folder 1.4)
- Letters home — from London, 1966-1968 (Folder 1.5)
- Letters home — from London and New York, 1976 (Folder 1.6)
- Vassar Memorabilia, 1962-1966 (Folder 1.7)
- Legal case against Reed Books for publication of "The Invited,", 1997 (Folder 1.8)
- Miscellaneous (Folder 1.9)
- Recording of Poetry Now, broadcast on BBC III, 1985 May 3 (Folder 1.10)
- Various journal publications, 1980-2010 (Box 2)